<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eurecom Movie Club</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://bde.eurecom.fr</link>
    <atom:link href="http://bde.eurecom.fr/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It's on!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The cinema season has now officially started, the movie club has shown it&amp;#39;s first movie of the
season (ever?), and more are in the planning. The board will get together to hammer out the program
for the season, or maybe only on a month-by-month basis, this remains to be seen. If you have any
suggestions to movies, we want to here from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little note about what we want to be. The movie club is intended to expose people to good movies
they wouldn&amp;#39;t normally come across. We do not intend to compete with cinemas and show mainstream
stuff, we&amp;#39;re looking for the gems that slip under the huge media radar, or older stuff that &amp;quot;kids&amp;quot;
these days haven&amp;#39;t heard of. The intention is that regular participation in the movie club will
be part of your cultural education, exposing you to classics, must-sees from a couple of decades
back, and also try to provide some context for each movie; why are we watching this? Is it because
of the surroundings of it&amp;#39;s creation? Was it, like &amp;laquo;&lt;strong&gt;Blair Witch Project&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;raquo; or
&amp;laquo;&lt;strong&gt;Primer&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;raquo;, made on a really small budget? Did it capture the theme of the period it
was made? Is it a lesser known brain child of a director famous for other things? We want to give
you a couple of these hooks to put each movie on, maybe some funny trivia or backstories you
haven&amp;#39;t heard, a little extra layer in addition to just watching movies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds interesting? Cool! Come drop by next Friday, we&amp;#39;ll be screening the naval action drama
&amp;laquo;&lt;strong&gt;Master and Commander&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;raquo; from 2007.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://bde.eurecom.fr/2014/03/16/its-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bde.eurecom.fr/2014/03/16/its-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
